Estefanx Roman Vazquez 900 Ruth Dr Bryant AR, 72022

Email: Stefanyroman@yahoo.com

Professional Summary

I am a hardworking and reliable worker focused on going above and beyond to support my team. Trained in the health industry and offering top-notch communication and fast pasting abilities. Motivated to continue to learn and grow in the health profession. Able to work with efficiency by paying attention to detail in order to be the fast learner that I am; to provide the best work without being in anyone's way.

Skills

- Bilingual (speak both fluent Spanish and English)
- Customer service payment processing
- Relationship building and customer understanding
- Communication skills excelling
- -3+Years Computer skills
- -Medical scribing for 3+ years
- -Currently enrolled in C++, HTML, and CSS programs
- Knowledge in patient skills using medical terminology and knowledgement in insurance help Fast pacing and organization skills

Experience

Baptist Health Internship Student, Dr. Rebecca- August 2018- May 2019

- Greeted visitors and escorted them to their destinations.
- Supported front office staff by providing word processing of correspondence and reports.
- Communicated regularly with external and internal patients to understand and meet their needs.
- Regularly shadowed a nurse, patient care tech, or was trusted and left unsupervised to visit patients independently. Providing them with any information I could assist on or with any needs they had.

Employer- Jonathan Muse May 2019-2021

Walgreens- Sales Associate- 8815 Stagecoach RD, Little Rock AR 72210 June 2020

- Provided accurate information to help customers quickly navigate, store and acquire items for

purchase. And help customers purchase, calculate prices, and process transactions. Unboxed and restocked merchandise into attractive displays.

Walgreens- Healthcare Customer Associate- 8815 Stagecoach RD, Little Rock AR

- Help the pharmacy with any kind of communication to help the Hispanic community. Attend the drive through window helping customers get their prescriptions and/or fill a prescription.
 - Fill in medications and place shipments where they belong.

Sherwood family medical center-Baptist Health-1308 E Kiehl Ave Sherwood, AR 72120 United States

June 2022-Current

- Medical Scribe/MA work.
- -Was in charge of coding all work including medications dosages, and alternatives, recommendations, and preventions.
- -Shadowing the doctors all day and recording and typing in all the information she'd say to her patients.

Education

Bryant High School- 801 N Reynolds Rd, Bryant AR 72022

- Gpa 3.75
- PreAp Classes and Ap classes from my freshman year to senior year
- Awarded Arkansas Scholars
- Student Varsity Soccer team- Freshman through Senior year
- Best Buddies Volunteer Program.
 - Creating a significant bond with special needs students in order to keep them company and active in their everyday school life.
- Member of Baptist collide with Bryant High school Program
- Graduated with a High School diploma

University Of Arkansas Pulaski Tech- 3000 W Scenic Dr, North Little Rock, AR 72118

- Was working on an associates of science until switching majors and university.

- Took Chemistry, Phycology, and Anatomy courses
- Completed two years at pulaski technical college

University Of Arkansas At Little Rock- 2801 S University Ave Little Rock, AR 72204 United States

- -Currently enrolled as a junior for the Computer Science program.
- -Continuing to exceed my skills and love for computers
- -Currently enrolled in Programming, Web Tech and other mathematical classes.